Hi, today, we're going to draw on coquille board.
On this one, it's a little bit more advanced.
I'm actually going to do a portrait.
A face of a woman.
Right now, I'm just going to go over the supplies you're going to need.
This is a sheet of coquille board, which is spelled c-o-q-u-i-l-l-e.
It's roughly five to six dollars a sheet but it's definitely worth the price.
I've got a number two pencil, which you can find in any drawer in your house.
I've got two colored pencils.
I've got a baby blue and I've got a dark black.
The black's the most important one.
I've got a gum eraser or some people call it a kneaded eraser.
And I've got two rulers.
I've got a clear measurement ruler and, well, I guess every ruler is a measurement ruler but you can see the measurements through and then this is just a regular metal ruler with a cork bottom.
I've got an electric pencil sharpener and I've got an Exacto blade to cut the board out when we get to that part.
Drawing table that has a, it's basically like a cutting mat on top of the table.
It's like a self-healing mat.
So, those are the supplies we're going to use today and I think you'll be pleased with the results.